Guide to the Martin Poll Papers MC.200
New York University Archives
Martin Poll Papers
1967-1984
New York University Archives
Poll, Martin
Martin Poll Productions
MC.200
40 Linear Feet
Martin Poll (1922-2012) was a New York-born film producer who opened a large movie studio in the Bronx in 1956. He sold the studio in 1961 and established his own production company, Martin Poll Productions, that went on to produce a number of well-known films, including the Oscar-winning The Lion in Winter in 1968. The collection contains documents pertaining to ten of his movies, including such materials as contracts, production reports, screenplay drafts, photographs, slides, sketches, call sheets, correspondence, and publicity materials.
Access Restrictions
Loan agreements, insurance certificates, salary information and condition reports are permanently restricted. audio materials in the collection have not been digitized and are not accessible. Contact the University Archives for details.
Arrangement
The Martin Poll Papers are arranged chronologically in eleven series pertaining directly to specific productions. Series contain boxes that are arranged both in legal and letter sized folders and are arranged alphabetically. The basic arrangement scheme reflects the original arrangement of these records and in most places original order was maintained.
The series arrangement of the records is as follows:
Missing Title
The Lion in Winter (1968)
The Appointment (1969)
The Man Who Loved Cat Dancing
Night Watch (1973)
The Sailor Who Fell from Grace (1976)
The Dain Curse (1978)
Stunt Seven (1979)
Nighthawks (1981)
Arthur the King (1985)
Gimme an F! (1984)
Projects
Biography of Martin Poll
Martin Poll was a film producer born in New York City on November 24, 1922. Graduating from the University of Pennsylvania in 1943 with a bachelor's degree in business, he served in the army before returning to work with his aunt Selma Tamber, a Broadway producer. Poll begun his film career in 1954 when he produced 39 episodes of the miniseries Flash Gordon in Europe. In 1956 Poll opened the Gold Medal Studios on East 175th Street in the Bronx, the former site of Biograph Studios, a silent movie studio. Gold Medal Studios become one of the largest movie studios outside of Hollywood, helping to revitalize film production in New York in the 1950s and 1960s. In 1959 Poll was made Commissioner of Motion Picture Arts of the City of New York and is credited with being a large influence in the creation of the New York City Film Commission. In 1961 Poll sold his studios and moved to Hollywood to engage in production full time. He went on to create his own production company, Martin Poll Productions, and continued to produce movies in California, New York, and internationally for the rest of his life. Poll produced a total around a dozen feature films, including the 1968 Oscar-winning drama The Lion in Winter, and a number of television productions, including the 1978 CBS miniseries The Dain Curse. Later in his career Poll served on the Tisch School of the Arts Advisory Council from 1978 to 1984. He died on April 14, 2012, at the age of 89.
Provenance
The Martin Poll Papers were donated to the George Amberg Memorial Film Study Center in The Tisch School for the Arts sometime following Poll's resignation from the TSOA Advisory Council. They were transferred to the NYU Archives in 2006.
Scope and Contents
The Martin Poll Papers contain documents and materials pertaining to the conception, production, and distribution of movies, TV movies and TV miniseries that his production company, Martin Poll Productions, produced from the late 1960s to the mid 1980s. These materials includes contracts, production reports, progress reports, screenplay drafts and revisions, distribution agreements, movie title registrations, press releases,, photographs, slides, sketches, correspondence, budgets, call sheets, press clippings, publicity materials, casting documents, insurance documents, breakdown sheets, reviews, permits, and schedules.
Deaccession Note
Portfolio "Art Materpieces" Series I, released by the Book of the Month Club removed from the collection.
Motion pictures |x Production and direction.; Harvey, Laurence; Goldman, James; Lenya, Lotte; Harvey, Anthony, 1931-; Aimée, Anouk, 1932-; Legrand, Michel, 1932-; Hepburn, Katharine, 1907-2003; O'Toole, Peter, 1932-2013; Everett, Rupert; Bergen, Candice, 1946-; Donner, Clive, 1926-2010; Hammer, Jan; Reynolds, Burt; Cannon, Dyan; Merrow, Jane; Salter, James; CBS/Broadcast Group (New York, N.Y.); Universal Pictures (Firm); Cannes Film Festival; Writers Guild of America; Academy of Motion Picture Arts and Sciences; Screen Actors Guild; Williams, Billy Dee; Neeson, Liam; Howard, Trevor, 1916-1988; Khambatta, Persis; Lloyd, Christopher, 1938-; Hauer, Rutger, 1944-; Stallone, Sylvester; Wagner, Lindsay; Durham, Marilyn; Kristofferson, Kris; Hopkins, Anthony, 1937-; Dalton, Timothy, 1944-; Straight, Beatrice; Coburn, James; Mishima, Yukio, 1925-1970; Hammett, Dashiell, 1894-1961
- Series I: The Lion In Winter (1968), 1966-1969
  - Academy Awards, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Ardmore Studios, 1967 November (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Artwork, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Barry, John, 1967 October-1968 April (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Budget, 1967 November-1969 March (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Casting, 1967 March-December (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Castle, John, 1967 October-1968 March (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Clipping and Publicity, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Costumes, 1967 September-1968 January (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Credits, 1968 April-August (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Crew, 1967 October-December (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Dalton, Timothy, 1967 October-December (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Directors, 1966 November-1967 March (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Film Production Association of Great Britain, 1967 November-1968 February (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - France, Location Information, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Furniture, Photographs, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Goldman, James, 1967 April-1969 March (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Harvey, Anthony, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Hepburn, Katherine, 1967 September-1968 April (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Hopkins, Anthony, 1967 October-December (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Insurance, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Legal - Contracts, Various, 1967-1969 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Legal - Correspondence, 1967 March-1969 June (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Legal - Embassy Pictures, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - McCall, Monica, 1966 October-1967 November (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Merrow, Jane, 1967 October-1968 January (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Morris Agency, 1967 December-1968 April (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Music, 1967 January-1968 November (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Nusbaum, Jane, 1967 November-1968 February (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - O'Toole, Peter, 1967 October-1968 March (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Press, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Production, 1967 October-1968 May (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Research, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Set and Properties, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Stock, Nigel, 1967 November-December (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Story Rights, 1967 November (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Terry, Nigel, 1967 October-December (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Titles, 1967 January-1968 April (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Young, Terence, 1968 April-August (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Series II: The Appointment (1969), 1966-1969
  - Aimee, Anouk, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Budget, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Budget Ledger - Suppliers, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Breakdown Sheets, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Cannes, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Contracts, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Cast, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Costumes, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Crew, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Daily Diary, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - General Ledger - Dollars, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - General Ledger - Lire, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Hawthorn Production, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Insurance, undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Legrand, Michel, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Locations, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Lotte, Lenya, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Lumet, Sydney, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - MGM - California, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - MGM - Contracts, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - MGM - London, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - MGM - New York, 1967-1969 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - MPAA, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Music, 1967-1969 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Negatives, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Press Kit, undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Production, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Production Budget, 1966-1968 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Production Reports, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Publicity, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Revisions 10/6/1966 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Salter, James, 1965-1968 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Segal, Mort, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Sharif, Omar, 1967-1969 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Sound, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Tassara Orazio, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Titles, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Weiss, Nat, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Series III: The Man Who Loved Cat Dancing (1973), 1972-1973
  - Accounting Binder, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Accounting Binder -- Contact Sheets, 1 of 5, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Accounting Binder -- Contact Sheets, 2 of 5, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Accounting Binder -- Contact Sheets, 3 of 5, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Accounting Binder -- Contact Sheets, 4 of 5, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Accounting Binder -- Contact Sheets, 5 of 5, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - American Indians, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - "Authentic American Indian Music" - From New York Public Library - 7" Reel, Record 1, 1973 (Box 25)
  - "Authentic American Indian Music" - From New York Public Library - 7" Reel, Record 2, 1973 (Box 25)
  - "Authentic American Indian Music" - From New York Public Library - 7" Reel, Record 3, 1973 (Box 25)
  - "Authentic Cowboys and their Western Folksongs" - Audio Cassette, undated (Box 25)
  - Bolt, Robert, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Budgets, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Casting, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - "Cat Dancing Theme" - [Jonny?] William - Piano Track - 5" Reel -, undated (Box 25)
  - Contracts, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Credits, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - "Dances of the North American Indians" - From New York Public Library -7" Reel, 1973 (Box 25)
  - "Dances of the North American Indian" Side 1-2 and "The Song of the Then Indian" Side 1-2 - Audio Cassette, undated (Box 25)
  - Directors, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - "Dream Away" - 5" Reel, undated (Box 25)
  - Durham, Marilyn, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - "Great Basin: Paiute, Washo, Ute, Bannock, Shoshone" From New York Public Library - 7" Reels, Side B, 1973 (Box 25)
  - "Great Basin: Paiute, Washo, Ute, Bannock, Shoshone" From New York Public Library - 7" Reels, Side A, 1973 (Box 25)
  - "Great Basin, Paiute Coyote Song and Ute Turkey Song" and "The Ballad Huner" - Audio Cassette, undated (Box 25)
  - Locations, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Miles, Sarah, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Music, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Perry, Eleanor - Screenwriter, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Premiere 6/26/1973 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Publicity Clips, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Reviews, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Reynolds, Burt, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Script 10/31/1972 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Script 1/17/1973 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Synopses, Bios, and Pre-Production Notes, undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Titles, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - "Tunes of the West" - Ray Mace - 7" Reel, Roll 1 of 2, Undated (Box 25)
  - "Tunes of the West" - Ray Mace - 7" Reel, Roll 2 of 2, Undated (Box 25)
  - Whiting, David A.' Death, Press Clips, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Series IV: Night Watch (1973), 1972-1973
  - Artwork, undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Casting, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Contracts, signed, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Costumes, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Credits, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Crew, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - George, George W. and Bernard S. Straus, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Harvey, Laurence, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Lang, Robert, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Literary Purchase Agreement with Lucille Fletcher, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Locations, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - MPAA Ratings, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Music, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Press Releases, undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Production, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Props, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Publicity, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Reviews, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Screenplay by Evan Jones 5/12/1972 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Script Breakdown 5/22/1972 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Slides, negatives, and 1 print, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Taylor, Elizabeth and Inter-Planet, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Title Registration, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Whitelaw, Billie, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Series V: The Sailor Who Fell from Grace with the Sea (1976), 1974-1977
  - Academy Members Invitations, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - AVCO Agreements, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - AVCO Correspondence, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - AVCO Payment Instructions, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Beaupre, Lee - Promotion, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Budget, First Preliminary, undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Budget, Secondary Preliminary, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Budget, Third Preliminary, undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Breakdown Sheets, undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Call Sheets, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Casting, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Casting, Bruce Dern, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Casting, Charlotte Rampling, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Completion Bonds, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Cross Plot, undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Daily Production Reports, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Distribution Statement, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Foreign Reviews, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Hawthorn, Ted - Production Designer, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Heller Agreement, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Insurance, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Kristofferson, Kris - General, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Kristofferson, Kris - in "Alice Doesn't Live Here Anymore", 1975 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Legal, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Literary Rights, Option Agreement, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Miles, Sarah, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Miscellaneous, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Mishima, Yukio - General, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Music, 1976-1978 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Nippon Herald, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Playboy Magazine, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Poll-Carlino Joint Venture 7/1/1974 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Poster Announcement, Circa 1975-1977 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Production, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Production Agreements, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Progressive Schedules, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Publicity (1 of 2), 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Publicity (2 of 2), 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Publicity, Biographies, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Publicity Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Publicity, Al Hix, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Publicity Materials Masters, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Publicity, Photographs, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Publicity, Promotion, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Rating, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Reviews, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Rights, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Screenplay 1/20/1975 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Screenplay, Master 8/30/1975 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Sea Dream - Cassette Tape, 1975 December 12 (Box 25)
  - Sheet Music, 1 of 5, Circa 1974-1976 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Sheet Music, 2 of 5, Circa 1974-1976 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Sheet Music, 3 of 5, Circa 1974-1976 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Sheet Music, 4 of 5, Circa 1974-1976 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Sheet Music, 5 of 5, Circa 1974-1976 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Sheet Music (Large), 1 of 2, Circa 1974-1976 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Sheet Music (Large), 2 of 2, Circa 1974-1976 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Storyboard, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Synopses, undated (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Titles, undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Treatment, Master 11/20/1974 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Walter E. Heller Factors, Inc., 1976 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Series VI: The Dain Curse (1978), 1974-1978
  - Bible, undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Bills, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Bills, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Book 2 (Binder), 1 of 2, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Book 2 (Binder), 2 of 2, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Budget (1 of 2), 1977 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Budget (2 of 2), 1977 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Budget, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Call Sheets 10/3 - 11/2/1977 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Call Sheets 11/4 - 12/20/1977 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Camera Reports, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Cannes, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Cast, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Cast List, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Casting and Personnel, 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - CBS, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - CBS Promotion, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Chabrol, Claude - French Director, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Characters, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Cinemobile, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Clippings (Binder), 1977 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Clippings (Leather Binder), 1977 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Clippings and Script Miscellaneous, 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Congdon, Don - Rights Agreement, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Contact Sheets, 1 of 4, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Contact Sheets, 2 of 4, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Contact Sheets, 3 of 4, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Contact Sheets, 4 of 4, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Continuity Days, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Costume Breakdown, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Costumes, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Credits, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Crew List, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Dailies and Director's Notes (Binder), 1 of 2, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Dailies and Director's Notes (Binder), 2 of 2, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Daily Actor Contracts, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Daily Production Report (Originals), 1977 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Daily Production Reports 10/3 - 10/14/1977 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Daily Production Reports 10/15 - 1/27/1977 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Daily Production Reports 10/28 - 11/9/1977 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Daily Production Reports 11/10 - 11/22/1977 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Daily Production Reports 11/23 - 12/6/1977 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Daily Production Reports 12/7 - 12/20/1977 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Day Out of Days, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - deForest Research, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Director's Television Agreement, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Easton, Pennsylvania - General, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Eaves Costumes Co., Inc., 1977 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Financing, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Foreign Contracts, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Foreign Distribution, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Foreign Sales, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Gerrity, Bill - Co-Producer, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Goodman, George - Production Manager, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Gunshot Schedule, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Dashiell Hammett's Book Covers, undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Dashiell Hammett's "The Continental Op" Review, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Dashiell Hammett Press, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Financial, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - First Draft, First Two Hours, Master, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Homeowner on Shelter Island, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Insurance, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Insurance, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Locations, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Locations by Page Count, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Log (1 of 2), 1977 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Log (2 of 2), 1977 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Memos, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous Materials, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Movielab, Inc., undated (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Music Inquiries, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Music Reviews, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Music Sheets (Set), Circa 1976-1978 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Music Sheets, 1 of 2, Circa 1976-1978 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Music Sheets, 2 of 2, Circa 1976-1978 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - NYC Memos, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Night Exteriors, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Omitted and New Scenes, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - One-Liner, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Paperback Edition, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Photos, undated (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Pinkerton's, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Post-Production, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Pre-Bible, undated (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Presentation Booklets, undated (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Press Clippings, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Press Releases, undated (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - "Private Eye" Transcriptions on Cassette, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - "Private Eye" Transcripts, undated (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Production, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Program Practices, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Program Formats, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Property Releases, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Property Release, signed, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Publicity, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Ratings, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Research, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Resumes, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Reviews, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Rights Agreement, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Selznick, Joyce - Casting, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Screen Actors Guild, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Screen Actors Guild Memos, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Screen Actors Guild Production Timesheets, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Screening, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Script, Part I Revised 3/30/1977 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Script, Part II Revised 3/30/1977 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Script, Part I 8/15/1977 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Script, Part II 8/15/1977 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Script, Part III 8/15/1977 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Script, Parts I-III Master 9/30/1977 (1 of 2) (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Script, Parts I-III Master 9/30/1977 (2 of 2) (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Script, Part II Draft, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Script, Part III Draft, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Script Timings, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Shear, Barry - Director, 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Shear, Wendy - Assistant Director, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Shelter Island Accommodations, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Shelter Island Contacts, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Shelter Island Locations, undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Shelter Island Police, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Shooting Schedule (1 of 3), 1977 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Shooting Schedule (2 of 3), 1977 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Shooting Schedule (3 of 3), 1977 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Show #1 and #2 Sound Transcriptions on Cassette, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Show 1 Line Script (Binder), 1 of 2, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Show 1 Line Script (Binder), 2 of 2, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Show 2 Line Script (Binder), 1 of 2, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Show 2 Line Script (Binder), 2 of 2, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Show 3 Line Script (Binder), 1 of 2, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Show 3 Line Script (Binder), 2 of 2, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Show #3 Sound Transcription on Cassette, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Slides -- Beatrice Strait, Circa 1977-1978 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Slides -- Ben, Circa 1977-1978 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Slides -- Cobert, Circa 1977-1978 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Slides -- Ellis Raab, Temple (Nancy), Circa 1977-1978 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Slides -- Hand Mount, Circa 1977-1978 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Slides -- Hand Mount?, Circa 1977-1978 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Slides -- Hand Mount 400, Circa 1977-1978 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Slides -- Jason Miller, Circa 1977-1978 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Slides -- J. Simmons (Chair), Circa 1977-1978 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Slides -- Jean Simmons, Circa 1977-1978 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Slides -- Kills, Circa 1977-1978 (Box 29, Folder 11)